Suppose we want to open a student cafe in New York.
 We would like to take into account the number of students, their specialties and nationalities.
For what purpose? 
We would like to find a good location, take into account the taste preferences in the menu, as well as organize a 
small library with books in different languages ​​and in different specialties. 
The necessary statistics in the form of histograms, totals and csv files can be obtained from the site https://datausa.io.
We will use the Foursquare API to explore neighborhoods in New York.
 Use the exploration function to get the most common categories of objects in each district,
 and then use this function to group the regions into clusters. 
We will use the k-means clustering algorithm to complete this task. 
Finally, we will use the Folium library to visualize New York neighborhoods and their new clusters.